<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<element>
    <sentence>I made a snow angel today.</sentence>
    <sentence>I was on a morning walk when I stepped on dog poop.</sentence>
    <sentence>I bought a bag of candy to celebrate a good grade I got from a test.</sentence>
    <sentence>I went for a walk with my friend.</sentence>
    <sentence>I ate a hamburger and French fries and now I feel tired.</sentence>
    <sentence>I went to a hip-hop dance class with my best friend.</sentence>
    <sentence>I went for a run when it was raining.</sentence>
    <sentence>I called an old school friend.</sentence>
    <sentence>I read a good fantasy book.</sentence>
    <sentence>I watched a great action movie.</sentence>
    <sentence>I watched a terrible kids movie.</sentence>
    <sentence>I made my favorite food on Friday.</sentence>
    <sentence>I listened to country music at a cabin.</sentence>
    <sentence>I played my favorite song on the guitar.</sentence>
    <sentence>I took a vacation trip with my friends.</sentence>
    <sentence>I played my favorite childhood game for the first time in years.</sentence>
    <sentence>I started learning to play the piano.</sentence>
    <sentence>I posted my own meme to Reddit’s r/dankmemes subreddit and I got over 100k upvotes.</sentence>
    <sentence>I saved some of my summer job salary and I bought an electric scooter.</sentence>
    <sentence>I took part in a raffle and won a case of my favorite soda.</sentence>
    <sentence>I started learning Spanish.</sentence>
    <sentence>I watched my favorite series on Netflix.</sentence>
    <sentence>I went cycling on a beautiful summer day.</sentence>
    <sentence>I crashed into a ditch with my bike but fortunately I had a helmet on.</sentence>
    <sentence>After being outside the whole day I slept like a log.</sentence>
    <sentence>My morning started by sprinting to the bus stop again.</sentence>
    <sentence>I had lunch with my mother in a new Chinese restaurant.</sentence>
    <sentence>I’m excited to go fishing with my grandfather again.</sentence>
    <sentence>Yesterday I stopped to watch the stars for a moment.</sentence>
    <sentence>I put seeds on my yard for the birds.</sentence>
    <sentence>It’s nice to wake up refreshed before the alarm clock rings.</sentence>
    <sentence>I was only supposed to wash the dishes, but I ended up cleaning the whole apartment.</sentence>
    <sentence>I played my own song to my friends.</sentence>
</element>